{
    "subject": "resource/Kingdom_of_Galicia\u2013Volhynia",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Halych",
    "human_readable": "The capital of the Kingdom of Galicia\u2013Volhynia is Halych.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9696070551872253,
            "question": "What was the capital of the Kingdom of Galicia\u2013Volhynia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9625769853591919,
            "question": "Name the city that served as the capital of Galicia\u2013Volhynia."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8924028277397156,
            "question": "What kingdom had Halych as its capital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7977443337440491,
            "question": "What is known about the Kingdom of Galicia\u2013Volhynia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7327470183372498,
            "question": "During which historical period was Halych the capital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6319186091423035,
            "question": "Were there any famous rulers from the Kingdom of Galicia\u2013Volhynia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46961742639541626,
            "question": "Is Halych a city or a country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.465730756521225,
            "question": "Where was Halych located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3982222378253937,
            "question": "How did the location of Halych influence the kingdom's development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10159316658973694,
            "question": "What were some important events that took place during the reign of the kingdom?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The capital of the Kingdom of Galicia\u2013Volhynia is Halych.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9085_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did the location of Halych influence the kingdom's development?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9085_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Halych located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9085_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Halych a city or a country?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9085_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9085_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9085_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9085_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9085_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9085_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9085_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9085_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9085_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9085_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9085_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support that Halych was indeed the capital of the Kingdom of Galicia\u2013Volhynia until the early 14th century, which aligns with the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}